<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Campsite Reservations Project</title>
    <link>http://awayfromho.me/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Campsite Reservations Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017 Corey Beres</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 17:46:29 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://awayfromho.me/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Jigsaw Puzzle</title>
      <link>http://awayfromho.me/blog/posts/the-jigsaw-puzzle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 17:46:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://awayfromho.me/blog/posts/the-jigsaw-puzzle/</guid>
      <description>Since my last update at the beginning of October, I updated the REST controllers to read data from a database (PostgreSQL in this case). Previously they read from data stored in a Java array.
Querying the database Spring makes it very easy to read from a database using JPA. I chose to use this approach. Spring handles all of the implementation. It does the basics (create, read, update, delete), and it can generate more complex queries based on functions&amp;rsquo; names.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vue.js Testing</title>
      <link>http://awayfromho.me/blog/posts/vue-js-testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 22:21:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://awayfromho.me/blog/posts/vue-js-testing/</guid>
      <description>Since my last update, I added new mock services to the Spring backend and new components to the Vue.js frontend. I added mock campsite, area, and availability services, and I added to the mock campground service. I added (real, not mock) controllers for those services. In the frontend, I added the campsite, campsite-list, availabilty-calendar, and quick-availability components.
The Java changes were very straightforward. It&amp;rsquo;s trivial to keep fake data in memory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I&#39;ve Done So Far</title>
      <link>http://awayfromho.me/blog/posts/what-ive-done/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 22:05:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://awayfromho.me/blog/posts/what-ive-done/</guid>
      <description>As I said in my last post, I&amp;rsquo;ve already started working on my campsites project. I had already recorded two live programming sessions, but those videos are gone forever.
So far, I built a very simple static website. When I build RESTful services (that return mock data initially), I&amp;rsquo;ll use this website to display the data. The website is very simple and ugly right now. I&amp;rsquo;ll worry about the aesthetics later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Campsite Reservations Project</title>
      <link>http://awayfromho.me/blog/posts/campsite-reservations-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 21:07:09 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://awayfromho.me/blog/posts/campsite-reservations-project/</guid>
      <description>The goal of this project is to build a campsite reservations system from scratch. The project will allow users to
 learn about a campgrounds view available campsites reserve campsites pay for reservations manage paid reservations  I started this project to show off my talents as a software engineer. I&amp;rsquo;m currently employed as a full-time software engineer, but I figure it can&amp;rsquo;t hurt to make something that will set me apart from other potential hires.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>